Your glasses.
Oh, uh, sorry.
Hey, Mr. Kanai and I...
We had sex.
A person who readily does what I can't.
She is robbing me of everything.
It makes no sense.
She doesn't even want it.
I wonder what it feels like for her.
You know, playing with other people's emotions.
It must feel good.
playing with other people's emotions i wonder if it's something that just feels so good you
can't ever give it up you can't imagine well then in that case i'm going to take everyone
obsessed with you and make them all my own then won't be even if it ends with somebody getting
hurt yeah i know even then i'm aware that i'm only thinking about my own satisfaction
but i just can't stop i must know i want all of the feelings that people have for her
i have to beat her at her own game if i don't do this i know i'm just going to become empty inside
feelings are things that one can just go around stealing or have stolen
shut up there's no way that doing this will make you feel fulfilled in any self-respecting way
just shut up already
i know that i'm pathetic
brat
i know i'm just being self-righteous
moogie i think we should start dating for real
yeah
we get along really well and we make a good couple
and eventually you'll fall in love with me too
why not come home with me now
no i can't
oh hanabi
what did you want
i get it
i know that i'm thoughtless and selfish
it's where i'm weakest
sanai
i've
i've decided to start dating moogie for real this time
but you're the only person that i
sanai you're the only one
i can't bring myself to use anymore
you're my friend
you're so very important to me
really
is that all it is
you can still use me
don't look at me like that
not at this point
you have to know by now
you have to have realized
that i am prepared for all of this
stop
that's enough
i won't see you after school alone anymore
really
okay
that's right
i've done something that i can't ever take back from her
i'm too scared to look now
i can't stand to look at what kind of face you're making
i'm sure i'm supposed to look
it's my responsibility
it's the least i can do for her
but then why
why me
i'll never
let you go
not now
my head is killing me
i didn't get a lot of sleep last night
oh did you want to go to the library as well hanabi
huh
all right then
sure
i feel like reading a book and it's way too noisy in here
let's go
i was thinking if you tell the teacher
hey you came along to join us too sanai
yeah i did
is that okay
sure be our guest
what
why now
oh
that's right
she's trying to act normal around me for my sake
we can do things at school though right
quiet
no talking in here
please
oh
i'm really sorry
i want you to forgive me
i completely took advantage of your longing for me
and pushed my own selfish desires and wishes on you
i deserve this punishment
you should have told me that you had a real fever hanabi
you didn't give me a chance to tell you
i'm sorry
no
we have to stop doing things like this
but there's nothing to worry about
nobody else knows about us
and i won't tell them anything
hey hanabi
why'd you start things up with mugi again
is it really to get your crush's attention
well there's
somebody that i like
no
that's not it
you're already so attractive
just the way you are now
who's worth going through all this trouble
it makes me jealous
that's not really true
it is true
what makes you so great
is your dangerous approach to life
trying to get a man to fall for you
that's easy
it grabs me
making me want to watch
watch you fill up with darkness
and then
no matter how corrupted or hurt you become
i will always accept you
all you have to do
is pretend to open up to them
but don't really
don't ever open up
you'll break
if you don't shut your true feelings out
what if i want them to know
my true feelings that is
just keep them to yourself
you can be the only one who knows about
your true feelings
in that moment
i don't know why
but i felt that she might say the same thing
so what then
what does that mean
what's an eye said
there was something so sad about it
so then
does that mean that
everyone's just as sad and lonely as i feel
even her
are you awake
can you go to the store for me
did i forget anything on her list
oh please excuse me
oh
you're akane's student
the guy from the diner
hey i can't believe you already forgot about me
you've really got some nerve
don't you ever touch me again
oh
that's right
he's one of akane's
pretend to open up to them
of course i remember you
so
you live nearby
trying to get a man to fall for you
that's easy
hey
i know
why not give me your number
oh
weren't you with your boyfriend at the diner
oh no
we're not really like that
oh
well in that case
why don't we
go hang out sometime
yeah
is that all i had to do
will pursuing the sky really fulfill me
hey
you're wearing your uniform
i just came from school after all
i'll play up this high school thing
you're pretty cute you know that
i bet you're told that a lot
uh i don't like where this is going
he's going to try to kiss me
no nobody has ever really said that about me
uh so
yes
that's right
if you don't mind
i was wondering about something
what's what's up with your relationship with miss minagawa anyway
huh
akane
uh
i mean nothing really
she's got others you know
she'll never really belong to me
so spend some time with me hanabi
what's with that
he's just one of many to akane
and he's fine with it being like that
i guess if it means he still gets to spend time with her
and now he's doing it to me
trying to recruit me over to his little harem of pathetic groupies
this won't do it all
this is just sad and pathetic and a waste of time
i must beat her
beat her to her own misery
so
i'm a
i'm a virgin
that turn you off
would you
ever be able to love me
i mean
why not me then
yes that's it
i need you to look at me like that
want me
shower me with all your love and devotion
have nothing left to give her
because you're mine
i don't know what it feels like to actually kiss someone that you love
is that sad
i guess it's the same as not knowing much in this world
you know
i mean it's just that
every time i'm touched
it's like
i realize i'm still just so empty inside
like i'm dead
so i continue to lock up my real feelings
hiding them deep down inside of me
making sure
that nobody ever knows the real me
you want to go to a motel
why would i
oh
i'm sorry
i just thought that you wanted to go
i promise i'll be gentle with you
that's not really the issue here
so what's the issue
uh
well
it's a matter of feelings
or something
well if the body feels good
then all of that emotional stuff will come
later
that might be the case
it feels really good when moogie and i always touch each other
especially thinking about brother
but
i'm sure that at some point
part of me must have started longing for moogie himself
i'm so pathetic
something bothering you
i'm fine
it's just that
what is it
i'm scared that things that feel good
will eventually make me really stupid in the end
do you understand me
and what's wrong with that
don't worry about it
i don't expect someone superficial like you to ever get it
that's harsh
maybe i should just leave
oh crap
he's just going to walk away from me
why am i making him go
why put on this front
are you not sexually confident in your abilities
then i guess that's all you'll ever be worth
nothing special ray
what's wrong
i'm sorry for being rude
it's just
i'm still scared
i see
i'm sorry
we'll take it slow
that was a close one
i almost just caved there for a sec
let's get to know each other
little by little
okay
i can pretend with you as much as you want
this is perfect
then you can fall for a fake version of me
i'll call later
i'm exhausted
but i learned something
unlike me and my unworthiness
she has enough self-respect
to have a high amount of self-worth
she truly is a monster
you can't shake it off her
i can't compare to her
here i am just crawling away
trying to get my self-respect
through other people's opinions
there's a big difference
placing my self-worth with other people
is never going to work
but the stupidity that forms it all
that makes people feel like their whole world will end
from the simplest of rejections
having the power to make them feel that way
isn't that love
people have been saying that daddy left us because i was born
who told you all of that nonsense
i heard my relatives telling my mom that
they said my daddy has a brand new family he likes to live with somewhere else
i guess he got tired and didn't want me anymore
you did absolutely nothing wrong
sometimes no matter how much you love someone
things just fall apart little by little
until you know you can't be together anymore
no matter how much you love them
like maybe even you and me
that is never going to happen between the two of us
do you promise?
yeah i mean because we'll never be romantic
i don't know what it feels like to actually kiss someone that you love
all right gather up
everyone to the gymnasium for the closing ceremony
yes
what's up?
wannabe's popular with guys
you better not let your guard down
let my guard down?
you did too, didn't you?
i did
no, that can't be
we just decided to go out for real
i don't know who she was with
but she must have ended it by now
am i already being cheated on here?
it probably has disappeared by now
so i'll leave another one
you want to come over to my place?
i can't
i have to get up real early tomorrow
she kissed like normal
maybe she got better at hiding it
this is rich
really to be honest
i feel like i'm being played right now
no
moogie
hey mocha
been a while
moogie please tell me you realize that that girl doesn't really want you
why are you always so honest
and not exciting
maybe you're right
and
if you cared
it actually loved her so much that it didn't bother you
i would be able to move on at last
but
i know you don't
so why can't it just be me instead?
okay sure
why not
want to go on a date?
come on
don't cry
i'm not the prince charming to your princess fantasies
maybe she'd cry more
maybe she'd cry more if i told her that
but that'd be going too far
i hate to admit it but i'm kind of soft on mocha here
let's go out
huh?
you know this is the first time you've ever really asked me out before
it's okay though
i love you enough to live with that
moogie
if i get in my bed and close my eyes
and maybe try and count a few sheep
by the time i wake up
it'll be the start of summer vacation
so
it just
just
yeah
they still
always
they do
that
but
it just
that
and
the
they just
thank you